zoopy.com 2007-12-10

# ::: Zoopy

Zoopy Privacy Policy  

In this day and age, online privacy and security have become non-negotiable and we want you to know that we’re 100% committed to protecting your privacy.

This Privacy Policy includes important information about the nature of information collected and used by Zoopy, and the methods used in the collection and use of this information.

It’s important that you read the policy carefully so that you’re able to make an informed decision about whether you’re happy to continue using Zoopy, and any of its subsidiary sites, and its services – all of which are covered by this Privacy Policy.

We do expect you to be honest when filling in personal details about yourself, and in compliance with the South African ECT bill, we have never, and will never reveal, share, or sell member information. Ever.

Please note that any video, image, or other content posted on Zoopy by its members and users, becomes published content and is not considered to be personally identifiable information subject to this Policy.

This Policy is also subject to change at any time, without any prior notice, so please check back often for any changes. 

By using this website or any of the services offered by Zoopy, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy, as well as our Terms and Conditions.

The information Zoopy collects & how we use it

User Provided Information

You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name, age and email address) to Zoopy when you sign up as a member and choose to make use of the services provided by Zoopy such as uploading and browsing videos or photos, posting comments, entering contests or sweepstakes, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists.

At no time shall we sell, trade, rent, use or otherwise disclose your personal information to a third party without your consent, except as provided for in this privacy policy. Only one exception to this applies: if you sign up via the BMW 1 Series website (http://www.bmw1series.co.za) then your data will be shared with BMW only.

And, by editing your profile, you are able to control which information you would like to protect, and how much information you make available to other Zoopy visitors.

You must understand that any personal information, video, or photo content that you voluntarily disclose online, becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others – so ensure that you edit your profile to control what information the public does, and does not, see.

Zoopy cannot be held liable for any damages resulting from your disclosure of personally identifiable information.

Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other visitors when you upload videos, photos, or send messages via Zoopy. 

Cookies

Just about every website that requires you to register and log in will use at least one cookie to store necessary information, specific only to you and your visit to their site. So know that when you visit the Zoopy site, we may send one or more cookies – a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters – to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser.

Please know that cookies cannot be used to access or collect any personal information and are merely used to help us understand how our visitors use the site, and to customise the website for each member. 

Any cookie information collected will never be revealed, sold to, or shared with, a third party.

Log file information

When you use Zoopy or any of our sites, our servers will – as is standard with most web servers – automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website.

These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the path followed through the website and, the amount of time spent on particular pages. 

This data is used to improve the quality and design Zoopy and its services, and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing user preferences and trends.

This information is also never revealed, shared or sold to any third party.

Do we ever disclose information?

We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with any third-party persons or companies for their commercial or marketing use without your prior consent.

We may however share non-personally identifiable, aggregated information with our channel sponsors in order to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality Zoopy. 

We will cooperate with any law enforcement enquiries, and we may be required to disclose information about you to law enforcement or other government officials to respond to claims or legal process. We may do this without your consent.

Please note that this Policy is subject to both South African laws, as well as the laws of the Country / State / City you reside in.

Our commitment to the privacy and safety of children

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important to us. For that reason, Zoopy does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13.

If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access Zoopy at any time, or in any manner. If Zoopy learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected, or appears anywhere on Zoopy without verified parental consent, we will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

Zoopy is also working in partnership with the SAPS and the SA Child Protection Unit in order to monitor suspicious activity and keep children safe from online predators. Please note that Zoopy will release any personally identifiable information required by the authorities in order to apprehend such criminals.

Contact Information

If you need any clarification on any section of this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by mailing: info@zoopy.com
